who do you see when you look in the
mirror
do you see someone who could be
achieving more in life
wouldn't it be great if you could
Unleash Your Potential and enjoy an
unlimited passive income stream that
will continue into your golden years
Manulife asset management is the global
Asset Management arm of a canadian-based
Manulife Financial Corporation or MFC
which has been in the business for more
than 125 years
mfc's vision is to be the most
professional Financial Services
organization in the world providing
strong
reliable trustworthy and
forward-thinking Financial Solutions for
our clients most significant financial
decisions
with Manulife Asset Management you'll
see a company with strong credentials
the kind of support you'll want behind
you unlike others we are part of a truly
Global team in Asia alone we have over
130 investment professionals managing
over 60 billion US dollars in assets
across 10 markets and over 300
investment professionals globally
managing around 250 billion US dollars
worth of assets across 17 countries and
territories
and to add to that our senior management
team has the experience knowledge and
global resources to help you build a
successful unit trust and private
retirement scheme or PRS business
at Manulife Asset Management we believe
that helping our clients achieve their
personal financial goals is more
important than fun returns despite that
we still manage to accumulate more than
20 fund awards from Lipper and
Morningstar
and because we believe you should have
an essential tool we've developed an
award-winning application you can't do
without the MHO a business application
tool that puts a world of resources in
your hands emichio helps me serve more
clients without compromising my quality
of service it helps me drill into their
portfolios to assess performance and to
make optimizing switches based on
Dynamic acid allocation as a
client-centric financial planner my
clients come first so as a Manulife unit
trust advisor I never leave home without
my MHO I don't know how any excellent
unit trust advisor can build a sizable
book of Business Without this tool
we offer a wide range of EPF approved
and Sharia compliant funds in Malaysia
we are the only company with a flexi
series which contains multiple funds
managed with the same objective but by
different fund managers as our unit
trust advisor not only your investors
have a choice of different fund managers
when investing in our flexi series you
will also have less worry in switching
or rebalancing your clients Investments
and we are one of only eight approved
private retirement scheme or PRS
providers in Malaysia
add Manulife Asset Management we
strongly believe that process is as
important as product this is why our
professional unit trust advisors are
well trained to use our proprietary
six-step process to get to know their
clients and understand their investment
needs before recommending the most
appropriate unit trust funds
soon what you'll find most rewarding is
our very attractive passive income or
asset-based commission ABC in fact our
top advisors now earn a passive income
at 33 000 Ringgit per month from their
asset-based commission and their total
income per year is as high as 1.4
million ringgit
at Manulife Asset Management your hard
work will be recognized at our grand
annual Awards night and you will be
incentivized with family orientated and
management-led holiday experiences to
Exotic destinations
at Manulife Asset Management we help you
build a successful unit trust and
private retirement scheme business one
that's going to take you closer to your
dreams so take a good look in the mirror
and make the right move with confidence
join us at manolife Asset Management
today and be our business fund